very specific outcome that is looking increasingly
unrealistic.
This is what I think is really annoying.
This blew my mind.
This is from Morningstar.
The S&P global ratings assigned these bonds.
So the loans that these private equity companies
are taking out to fund these data centers,
they assigned the bonds of investment grade rating of A+.
However, the debt yield is 6.58%.
OK.
That rate is typically associated with junk bonds.
So they're saying it's A+.
But what are their actions showing?
What does this remind you of?
Like this is the plot of a movie and a book
and something that actually happened.
I wrote.
It's giving subprime mortgages.
Yeah.
I know when I was reading this, I was like, God, this is,
I feel like I'm reading about the subprime mortgage crisis
in a book about the subprime mortgage crisis.
But it's happening right in front of me.